

# ANTONELLA DI TURRIS

**ENGINEERING STUDENT** 

## **PROFILE**

Engineering student with extensive professional experience in several fields, specialized in carrying out tasks simultaneously, in Spanish, English and Portuguese. Over the years I developed a great capacity for teamwork and effective communication.

I like challenges and I am currently doing IT training, focusing on developing my career in the systems and development area.

# SKILLS

Python	
Sql	
Javascript	
Html	
CSS	
Vue	
Bootstrap	
Looker Studio	
Excel	

## CONTACT

Address: Buenos Aires, Argentina Cell: 549-11-3481-2721 E-Mail: amditurris@hotmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/amditurris/

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Assistance Supervisor**

ASSIST CARD (04/2022 - 09/2022)

- Virtual supervision in night shift (00:00 to 08:00) to coordinators from Brazil, Peru and Argentina.
- Monitoring and evaluation of the performance of the coordinators, together with periodic feedback in order to improve it.
- Assignment and control of tasks based on the skills and strengths of each coordinator.
- Audit of cases and medical budgets, elevating to management what corresponds.
- Containment and resolution of complaints.

## **Assistance supervision support**

ASSIST CARD (11/2021 - 31-03-2022)

- Supervision support by helping Jr. coordinators in different situations.
- Daily administrative reports.
- Containment of customer complaints.

#### **Assistance Coordinator**

ASSIST CARD (09/2019 - 10/2021

- -Comprehensive assistance to clients through multiple platforms.
- -Medical coordination in Spanish, English and Portuguese all over the world.
- -Medical and cost evaluation with the indicated sectors.
- -Daily monitoring of hospitalized patients.

### **Customer Service Representative**

Berlitz Argentine (10/2017 - 03/2018)

- Reception, organization and collection at the language study center.

#### **Media Assistance**

Mediacom (08/2015 - 08/2016)

- Daily monitoring of the performance of advertising campaigns on various platforms.

#### Reception and manager

Nobel Salud (02/2013 - 04/2014)

- Administrative and in charge of external clinics.

#### **EDUCATION**

## 100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp

Udemy - (08/22 -present)

## **Big Data**

Codo a Codo 4.0 - (08/22 - 12/22)

## **Full stack - Python**

Codo a Codo 4.0 - (02/22 -07/22)

## **Chemical and Food Engineering**

UBA (2015 - present)

## **Automotive Mechanical and Electrical Technician**

ITCA (2014-2016)

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Advanced Portuguese Advanced Spanish Native